{
    "id": "dca2f2e61ffb4836a59d4fb57eeea761",
    "title": "Passive Voice Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The spider ......................................... by the boy.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "killed",
                "was killing",
                "was killed"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The thief ............................................ by the police.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "caught",
                "was caught",
                "was catching"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "A kite ......................................... by the boy.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "made",
                "was made",
                "was making"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The dog .......................................... by the sudden noise.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "frightened",
                "was frightened",
                "was frightening"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The light bulb ....................................... by Edison.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was invented",
                "invented",
                "was inventing"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "A very remarkable discovery ......................................... by him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "made",
                "was made",
                "was making"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He ........................................... by his own brother.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "betrayed",
                "was betrayed",
                "was betraying"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "My old car ........................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has told",
                "has been told",
                "was told"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The store .......................................... only last month.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "opened",
                "was opened",
                "was opening"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Smoking in the kitchen isnâ€™t ..........................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "permitting",
                "permitted"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The mouse ...................................... by the cat.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was chased",
                "was cheating",
                "cheated"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I .............................................. by your behavior.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "am disgusted",
                "am disgusting",
                "disgusted"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}